{
    "subject": "resource/Sterba_Propellers",
    "predicate": "property/locationCity",
    "object": "resource/Holmes_Beach,_Florida",
    "human_readable": "Sterba Propellers is located in Holmes Beach, Florida.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9005095958709717,
            "question": "Where is Sterba Propellers located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7777369022369385,
            "question": "In which state is Sterba Propellers found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7345543503761292,
            "question": "Is Sterba Propellers in a coastal city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6275961995124817,
            "question": "Are there any other businesses similar to Sterba Propellers in Florida?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4750903248786926,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist attractions near Holmes Beach, Florida?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47452491521835327,
            "question": "Can you name other businesses located in Holmes Beach, Florida?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3750133812427521,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Holmes Beach, Florida?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3136572539806366,
            "question": "What type of business is Sterba Propellers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31036800146102905,
            "question": "Does Sterba Propellers have a website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28639528155326843,
            "question": "What are propellers commonly used for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sterba Propellers is located in Holmes Beach, Florida.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6305_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Sterba Propellers have a website?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6305_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of business is Sterba Propellers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6305_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Holmes Beach, Florida?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6305_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6305_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "To evaluate the triple \"Sterba Propellers is located in Holmes Beach, Florida\", I'll look for information about the location of Sterba Propellers in the provided context.\n\nThe relevant documents are:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6305/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6305/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt\n\nIn the first document, it's mentioned that Sterba Propellers is a company, but there's no specific information about its location.\n\nIn the second document, it's mentioned that \"Sterba soloed in a Cessna 150 after joining a flying club 48 years ago.\" However, this doesn't provide any information about the location of Sterba Propellers.\n\nHowever, I found another relevant document:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6305/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt\n\nIn this document, there's a mention of \"AeroLux Propellers\" and then a list of companies, including \"Sterba Propellers\". However, there's no specific information about the location of Sterba Propellers in this document either.\n\nAfter reviewing all the documents, I found another relevant document:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6305/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt (same as the first one)\n\nIn this document, it's mentioned that Sterba Propellers is the brand name of a propeller shop, and specifically, \"The Ole Fahlin Memorial Propeller Shop...is the only FAA Authorized Repair Station for wooden propellers west of the Mississippi.\"\n\nHowever, I found another relevant sentence in this document:\n\n\"The shop currently specializes in the repair and refurbishment of wood propellers under the guidance of Herb Robbins. The shop still receives propellers for repair and refurbishment that were manufactured by Ole.\"\n\nBut no information about its location.\n\nThen I see a mention of Harry Myers who constructed N6119R, an aircraft with Sterba propeller, which was built in Willcox, Arizona.\n\nAnd then, I find another relevant document:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6305/re-ranker-msmarco/48.txt\n\nIn this document, there's a mention of Mark Steele who owns an aircraft with Sterba propeller (Sterba is the brand name), and it says \"Based out of Charlotte County Airport in Punta Gorda FL.\"\n\nGiven all these documents, I can say that there's no direct information about Sterba Propellers' location. However, I found a document where an aircraft owner has his plane based at Charlotte County Airport, but it is not explicitly stated whether this particular propeller shop (with the brand name Sterba) is also located in Punta Gorda FL.\n\nAfter reviewing all the documents, I can say that:\n\nResponse: {'output': 'no'}\n\nThe context information does not provide conclusive evidence to support or refute the triple \"Sterba Propellers is located in Holmes Beach, Florida\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided does not contain any details about the location of Sterba Propellers. Therefore, we cannot confirm that Sterba Propellers is located in Holmes Beach, Florida based on the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context to suggest that Sterba Propellers is located in Holmes Beach, Florida.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text provides information about Sterba Propellers being associated with aircraft, a flying club,  and a specific owner Mark Steele of Mesquite, Texas. It also mentions the company's history and specialization in wooden propellers repairs and refurbishments. There is no mention of Sterba Propellers being located in Holmes Beach, Florida.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the context information states that the Sterba Propellers is a manufacturer of aircraft propellers, not a location, and does not mention Holmes Beach, Florida.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Sterba Propellers being located in Holmes Beach, Florida. Sterba Propellers are mentioned as part of the list of companies that FreightCenter has shipped to, but no location for them is provided. Therefore, without additional evidence, we cannot confirm their specific location.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}